{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Awning Fabric Repair Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40455/":{"taskOID":40455,"originalTaskOID":40455,"setID":746,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5723,"questionDisplayText":"Location of Awning/Patio Cover","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where is the awning or patio cover installed? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7005,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Window(s)","answerDisplayText":"Window(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2033,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Door(s)","answerDisplayText":"Door(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4807,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Porch","answerDisplayText":"Porch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4604,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Patio","answerDisplayText":"Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1839,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Deck","answerDisplayText":"Deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4571,"questionDisplayText":"Repairs Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What needs to be done? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":645,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Add or repair motor","answerDisplayText":"Add or repair motor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":646,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Add or repair remote control","answerDisplayText":"Add or repair remote control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":649,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Add protective hood","answerDisplayText":"Add protective hood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":651,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Add screening","answerDisplayText":"Add screening","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":656,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Add sun or wind sensor","answerDisplayText":"Add sun or wind sensor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":659,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Add wind sensor","answerDisplayText":"Add wind sensor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":876,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Attach frame to house or window","answerDisplayText":"Attach frame to house or window","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5211,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Repair frame","answerDisplayText":"Repair frame","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5215,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Repair lateral arm","answerDisplayText":"Repair lateral arm","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5270,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Replace fabric","answerDisplayText":"Replace fabric","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5272,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Replace frame","answerDisplayText":"Replace frame","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5723,"questionDisplayText":"Location of Awning/Patio Cover","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where is the awning or patio cover installed? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7005,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Window(s)","answerDisplayText":"Window(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2033,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Door(s)","answerDisplayText":"Door(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4807,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Porch","answerDisplayText":"Porch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4604,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Patio","answerDisplayText":"Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1839,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Deck","answerDisplayText":"Deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":7005,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Window(s)","answerDisplayText":"Window(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2033,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Door(s)","answerDisplayText":"Door(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4807,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Porch","answerDisplayText":"Porch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4604,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Patio","answerDisplayText":"Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1839,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Deck","answerDisplayText":"Deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4571,"questionDisplayText":"Repairs Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What needs to be done? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":645,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Add or repair motor","answerDisplayText":"Add or repair motor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":646,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Add or repair remote control","answerDisplayText":"Add or repair remote control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":649,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Add protective hood","answerDisplayText":"Add protective hood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":651,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Add screening","answerDisplayText":"Add screening","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":656,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Add sun or wind sensor","answerDisplayText":"Add sun or wind sensor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":659,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Add wind sensor","answerDisplayText":"Add wind sensor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":876,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Attach frame to house or window","answerDisplayText":"Attach frame to house or window","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5211,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Repair frame","answerDisplayText":"Repair frame","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5215,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Repair lateral arm","answerDisplayText":"Repair lateral arm","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5270,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Replace fabric","answerDisplayText":"Replace fabric","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5272,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Replace frame","answerDisplayText":"Replace frame","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":645,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Add or repair motor","answerDisplayText":"Add or repair motor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":646,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Add or repair remote control","answerDisplayText":"Add or repair remote control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":649,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Add protective hood","answerDisplayText":"Add protective hood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":651,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Add screening","answerDisplayText":"Add screening","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":656,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Add sun or wind sensor","answerDisplayText":"Add sun or wind sensor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":659,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Add wind sensor","answerDisplayText":"Add wind sensor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":876,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Attach frame to house or window","answerDisplayText":"Attach frame to house or window","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5211,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Repair frame","answerDisplayText":"Repair frame","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5215,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Repair lateral arm","answerDisplayText":"Repair lateral arm","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5270,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Replace fabric","answerDisplayText":"Replace fabric","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5272,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Replace frame","answerDisplayText":"Replace frame","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40455/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40455,"taskName":"Fabric Awning or Patio Cover - Repair","taskDescription":"Repair Fabric Awnings or Patio Covers","xmTaskDescriptor":"Awning Fabric Repair Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":17,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Fabric window retractable covers porch","textMessagingName":"Repr Awn Fabric","rolloverLongDesc":"Awnings provide shade to exterior spaces as well as prevent hot summer sunshine from heating interior spaces \u0026 fading fabrics. Some units are retractable with a motor \u0026 or crank. Note separate categories for fabric awning installation, metal awnings, shutters \u0026 window tinting.","rolloverShortDesc":"Repair or replace fabric, frame or retraction parts.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair Fabric Awnings or Patio Covers.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Awning Fabric Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Fabric Patio Cover Repair","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":7,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Fabric Awning or Patio Cover Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Fabric Awning or Patio Cover - Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Awning Project","urlName":"Fabric-Awning-or-Patio-Cover-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Fabric Awning/Patio Cover Repair Pros - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"fabric awning, porch, awning, retractable awning, retractable, porch cover, fabric","emcCategoryOid":-12007,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":746,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false}}